I barely remember the joyful days of the past...
我幾乎沒法記起...
...that I spent wlth my mother.
...以往和媽媽在一起的快樂日子
After my mother's death...
媽媽去世後...
...I was put into a convent.
...我被送進一間女修道院
There I spent day after day...
在那裡的每一天...
...doing disgusting and degrading things for no reason.
...我都被迫去做些憎惡和墮落的事情
However, I made friends...
雖然如此，我還是交到一些朋友...
...who were very kind to me during those troubling times.
...他們在這段討厭的日子裡帶給我關懷
Beth...
貝絲...
...and Andrew, the love of my life.
以及我的至愛安德魯
Then one day, a man unexpectedly arrived to take me away to his home.
後來，有一個人突然來到並把我帶返家中
Duke Dusse, my mother's younger brother.
路積公爵，我的舅舅
It was delightful to meet a living relative...
能夠遇見世上的親人確實令人高興...
...and I decided to take his lessons and become a Love Doll...
...我決定接受他的訓練...
...the flower of high society.
...學習成為愛奴，社交界之花
But...
但是...
...I was forced to endure unimaginable lessons in sex.
...我要去忍受難以想像的性愛教程
In town one day...
某天在鎮裡...
...by chance...
...偶然地...
...I happened to see Andrew and Beth together, enjoying themselves...
...給我看見安德魯和貝絲在一起，十分親熱...
...and that was enough to make me worried and nervous.
...令我感到不安及困擾
Love Doll Episode 3
哀．奴隸 第三話
Next!
下一個！
Duke Dusee.
路積公爵
George. How is Rachel coming along?
喬治，莉露的狀況如何？
She's progressing quite nicely.
她進展良好
We're fine tuning her for the party the day after tomorrow.
我們正為後天的宴會而對她進行優化
Hmm...
唔...
So these are this year's Love Doll candidates.
這些就是今年的愛奴候選人
They appear to be good quality.
看來她們的質素都不錯
I wonder how many will make it through the testing?
不知會有多少人可以通過考驗呢？
It should be fun!
定會很有趣！
I... I'm sorry.
對...對不起
Are you alright, Rosalie?
妳沒事嗎，羅莎莉？
Huh? Lady Rachel.
啊？莉露小姐
What's wrong? You're not yourself recently.
什麼了？妳最近總是心不在焉的
I think you should ask for permission to take a break and get some air.
我認為妳應該去請求休息，讓精神回復
Yes... That would be best.
對...最好就這樣做
Lady Rachel, you're very admirable.
莉露小姐，妳真令人敬佩
What?
啊？
Here you are with worries of your own but still you stop to help me.
妳正為自己的事而憂心，還是停下來幫我
I have to keep up an attitude.
我一定要保持狀態
If I'm intimidated here, all my efforts will have been for nothing. I can't have that, right?
如果我這時就懼怕，我之前的努力就會白費
I've been working hard...
我決不能這樣，我一直在努力...
I don't want to waste that.
就是不想浪費這個機會
That girl...
這女孩...
Huh?
啊？
That's my younger sister.
她是我的妹妹
She was sold to another house and has been taking Love Doll lessons like you.
她被賣了給其它人，正接受著和妳一樣的愛奴訓練
Is that so?
竟然如此
It's been two years since we've seen each other.
我們已經兩年沒見面了
She's become so beautiful.
她現在變得很漂亮
Yes...
是呀...
She's also gone through some hard lessons.
她也一定接受過艱辛的訓練
Right.
對
She's never complained in her letters, but I can feel her pain.
她從沒在信中抱怨，不過我可以感受到她的痛苦
I know she's not as strong as you, Lady Rachel.
我知她不像莉露小姐妳那般強
When I think about how other girls have felt in past...
當我想到以往其它女孩的遭遇...
...I'm so worried about her.
...我就非常為她擔憂
Your sister will be alright. I'm sure she'll do fine on the test.
妳妹妹會沒事的，我肯定她在考驗中會有好表現
What?
啊？
It's just a hunch but...
只不過是直覺...
Lady Rachel!
莉露小姐！
That girl you're taking care of...
正受到你照顧的那個女孩...
She looks so much like your sister, the legendary Love Doll.
和你那個是傳奇愛奴的妹妹很相像
That's her daughter.
就是她的女兒
Really?! So that's why she looks like her.
真的嗎！怪不得如此像
It's time to start the test.
是時候開始考驗了
Feels good!
感覺真好！
She's a waste. She came by herself.
她是廢物，只會顧自己
You came too fast.
妳來得太快了
That's too bad.
這樣很差
This one's no good either.
這個亦好不到那裡去
Excuse me...
請問...
Huh?
啊？
Is something wrong?
請問是否出了問題？
No...nothing.
沒...沒事
You know so much. I don't really understand wine.
你的見識真廣，我對紅酒真的毫不瞭解
I really don't know how to enjoy the taste yet.
仍未知道如何去品嚐
But you're extremely intelligent.
不過以妳那極端的聰明
I'm sure if you put your mind to it...
我肯定妳只要放些心機...
...you could be a great wine taster and put any sommelier to shame.
...妳必可成為一位超卓的紅酒專家，叫酒侍也慚愧
You really know how to flatter a girl.
你真是懂得取悅女孩
Have you heard the rumor about Prince Andrew?
有聽過關於安德魯王子的謠言嗎？
Andrew?
安德魯？
What about him?
他如何了？
I heard he's dating the daughter of the Taylor family.
聽說他和泰勒家的女兒約會
Yes, I heard the royal house will soon make an announcement about the Prince's marriage.
是的，聽說皇室將會對王子的婚姻發出通告
She must be his fiancйe.
她一定是他的未婚妻
The daughter of the Taylor family...
泰勒家的女兒...
That's Beth.
這是貝絲
Well...
好了...
We should go and begin your test now.
我們現在應該要去開始妳的考驗
Yes...
是...
Is something wrong?
有問題嗎？
You don't feel well?
妳不舒服嗎？
N... no.
不...
This is no good. I'm a Love Doll candidate.
不行，我現在是愛奴候選人
This is not the time to worry about other things.
沒時間去想其他事情了
Relax! No need to rush!
放鬆！不用急！
It's starting to get good. I can't tell you how great this feels.
開始有快感了，這種感覺真是難以形容的好
This is awesome!
這真是出乎意料！
Her mouth... sucking me off... not even coming up for air.
她的嘴...一直在吸吮...完全不用喘息
I haven't had it this good in a long time.
好久沒嚐過這種快感了
Anli!
不行了...
Amazing!
令人驚訝！
She acts like she's about to come but then gets right back to work.
她似乎達到了高潮，但又可迅速返回崗位
I can't figure out if she's faking it or not.
分不出是否假裝
Ah... Anli...
呀...不行了...
Your cock is so far inside me!
你的大雞雞深入我裡面了！
Touching the back wall of my pussy...
碰到我小屄屄的底壁了...
Ah... I can't hold it... Do you mind if I come?
呀...我忍不住了...妳介意我現在就來嗎？
N...no. I'm going to come too.
來吧...我也要高潮了
Anli... How great...
不行了...好爽呀...
You!
妳！
What... what's your name?
妳...妳叫什麼名字？
I'm simply Love Doll candidate number three.
我純粹是愛奴候選人三號
I can't tell you my name just yet.
我不能告訴你名字的
Rachel, you did well.
莉露，妳做得很好
You had many compliments from the party.
在這次宴會裡，妳受到不少讚賞
You also had the best score of all the candidates.
妳亦同時在眾多候選人當中獲得最佳分數
I'm very proud of you.
我以你為榮
Thank you very much.
多謝讚賞
I was so worried about Andrew and Beth.
我對安德魯和貝絲的事十分掛心
But I still had sex with strangers without hesitating.
但我仍然可以毫不猶豫地和陌生人做愛
Furthermore, I didn't only just give them pleasure. I enjoyed it as well.
而且我不單帶給他們快樂，我自己亦同樣享受
What a awful woman I am...
我真是一個可怕的女人啊...
From now on, your lessons will be over when you go to bed.
從現在起，當妳上床後，不用授課了
What?
啊？
You're usually forced to have sex, even while you were sleeping...
通常即使妳正在睡覺也要強迫做愛...
...but starting today you'll be allowed to sleep undisturbed.
...但現在允許今後不再騷擾妳睡覺
Duke Dusee! The purpose of our lesson is to take her to the extremes.
路積公爵！我們教程的目標是把她訓練成為極端
At this time, we should push her even harder than we have before.
在這時，我們對她應該要比以往更嚴格
Shut up, George!
住口，喬治！
Y... yes sir.
是...是的，大人
I am pleased.
我感到高興
I want to give her a little break.
想給她一個短暫休息
That is all.
僅此而已
I want to see Andrew. Find out if he's really getting married or not.
我要見安德魯，看他是否真的要結婚
Andrew is staying at the Royal Family's country home.
安德魯現時住在皇室的行宮
I'll have enough time to get there and back by morning.
我應該有充份時間在天光前回來
Lady Rachel?
莉露小姐？
What are you doing up this late at night?
都這樣晚，妳還在做什麼？
Um... well...
唔...沒什麼...
Are you planning to leave the residence?
您要離開住所嗎？
Rosalie, there's something I have to find out.
羅莎莉，我有一些事要辦
I'll be back by morning.
我天光前會回來
Please let me go. Please!
請讓我去吧，求求妳！
The west gate is probably safest at this time.
此時西閘大概是最安全的
The gatekeeper usually gets drunk and passes out.
那個看門人通常會喝至酊酩大醉
Rosalie?
羅莎莉...
Come this way.
行這邊
Rosalie, why are you being so kind to me?
羅莎莉，為何妳要對我這樣好？
This is my thanks to you for cheering me up at the party.
妳在宴會中使我振作，這是給妳的感謝
Really?
真的嗎？
Yes.
是真的
I was very nervous because of my sister.
我妹妹令我感到非常不安
If you hadn't said something to me, I could have made a really big mistake.
如果沒有妳對我說的那些話，我定會犯上大錯
They might have thrown me out of this house.
也許我會因此給他們丟出這間屋
And how's your sister doing?
那妳妹妹的表現又如果？
Thanks for asking. She's doing fine, but not as well as you, Lady Rachel.
多謝關心，她做得很好，只是沒有莉露小姐妳那樣好
She did pass the test though.
她通過考驗了
Did she? That's great!
是嗎？那就太好了
Well, leave from here.
好了，從這兒離開
But please come back by morning.
但請天光前回來
I understand. Thank you, Rosalie.
我瞭解，多謝妳，羅莎莉
You didn't see me tonight.
妳今晚沒有看見過我
Alright?
行嗎？
Yes.
是
Please take care.
請保重
Lady Rachel.
莉露小姐
Was it really this far? It felt much closer when I went there during the day.
真的如此遠嗎？總是覺得那天近得多
Huh?
啊？
It... It can't be...
怎...怎會這樣...
Which way? Which way should I go?
那條路？我應該行那條路？
The sun's coming up.
天光了
I don't think I can make it back before people at the house start getting up.
我想我沒法在屋內的人起床前回到去了
What should I do?
怎樣辦？
But I've come this far. I really need to see Andrew, no matter what happens.
既然來到如此遠，無論如何，我也要見安德魯
Andrew, where are you? Where's the house?
安德魯，你在哪裡？
Huh?
啊？
Rachel?! Is that you?
莉露？是妳嗎？
Beth...
貝絲...
Really? So Andrew's not here?
真的是妳？哪安德魯不在這兒嗎？
He's living at the Royal University where he's studying the dynasties.
他現正在皇家大學，研習各個朝代
Beth...
貝絲...
What?
什麼了？
Is it true that you and Andrew are getting married?
妳和安德魯結婚是真的嗎？
What... What are you talking about?!
什麼...妳說什麼？
Don't believe those stupid rumors.
不要相信那些愚蠢的謠言
I haven't learned how to be a wife yet. I'm not ready to get married.
我仍未學習怎樣去做一個妻子，沒有結婚準備
I'll admit that I've met him a few times while he was staying here, but...
我承認在這裡和他見過幾次面，但是...
But...
但是...
...that's about it.
...就是如此
I'm so sorry. Sorry for doubting you.
很抱歉，懷疑了妳
N...no. There's no need to apologize.
不用...根本沒有道歉的需要
I am really sorry.
真是抱歉了
I'm the one who should be apologizing to you.
我才是應該要向妳道歉的人
What?
啊？
I have to be honest with you. It is true that I love Andrew.
我想對妳誠實，我真的喜歡安德魯
I know it's wrong to fall in love with your best friend's boyfriend...
我知道愛上好友的男朋友是不對的
But don't worry.
但不必擔心
It's you who Andrew loves. He still loves you, Rachel.
安德魯愛的人是妳，他仍深愛著莉露妳
He's tried everything he could to see you.
為了見妳，他已嘗試過所有方法
But your situation doesn't allow for you to see anyone.
不過妳的情況不允許妳見任何人
Even a member of the Royal Family.
即使是皇室成員
He's decided to wait until the day he can see you again.
他決定會一直等到可以再見妳的一天
My situation...
我的情況...
I... I took advantage of you.
我...我利用了妳
I thought that I could steal him away from you.
我想我可以從妳那兒把他搶走
It was only for a split second... and I didn't act on it. But...
這只是一瞬間的念頭而已，不會實行，但...
...I'm a horrible person for even thinking it. Do you hate me?
...但我仍然覺得自己可惡，妳會討厭我嗎？
Thank you, Beth.
感激妳，貝絲
You told me the truth from your heart, even though it must have been hard to admit.
儘管很難去承認，妳也對我說出了真心話
You really are my best friend.
妳真是我最好的朋友
Rachel... you forgive me?
莉露...妳原諒我嗎？
There's nothing to forgive.
根本就沒有什麼要去原諒
Rachel...
莉露...
Beth...
貝絲...
We shouldn't be doing this.
我們不應做這種事
We did it once before at the convent.
我們以前在修道院都做過一次
Beth, you and I are still best friends now. Nothing's changed...
貝絲，現在妳和我仍是最好的朋友，什麼也沒變...
But...
不過...
I can't...
我不行了...
It's okay, Beth. Enjoy this as much as you want.
沒事的，貝絲，來盡情享受吧
I'm happy just making you feel this way.
好高興可以令妳感受一下這種方式
R... Rachel!
莉...莉露！
Rachel! No, it's dirty down there...
莉露！不要，往下那處很污髒的...
It's alright. It's your ass, Beth. There's nothing dirty about it.
沒事的，那是貝絲妳的屁屁，一點兒也不污髒
It... It feels strange. It tickles... and I'm getting so hot...
感覺好奇怪...有點癢...身體好熱...
Amazing! Beth, you're so wet.
真驚奇，貝絲，妳那處好多水呀
Rachel, please! Don't say things like that.
莉露，求求妳！別說這種話
This is great!
這樣才棒！
Beth, can you do the same things to me? Please!
貝絲，妳可否跟我做同樣的事？求求妳！
Y...Yes. Ok.
好...好的，可以
I love you so much, Beth.
我好喜歡妳，貝絲
I love you too, Rachel.
我也一樣喜歡妳，莉露
Yeah. Yeah. I remember now.
對了，對了，我現在想起了
That time the principal's face got like that.
這時候校長的臉就會這個樣子
Excuse me.
打擾了
There's someone here to pick up Lady Rachel.
有人要帶莉露小姐走
Pick her up?
帶她走？
This way, sir.
這邊，先生
I've come to take you home...
我來帶你回家的...
...Lady Rachel.
...莉露小姐
No... no!
不...不要！
Rachel?
莉露？
Yes.
是
Rosalie!
羅莎莉！
Quickly! We have to get her to a doctor! She'll die!!
快給她看醫生！她快耍死了！
Shut up! It's too late to call a doctor.
住口！現在找醫生已經太遲了
Uncle! It's my fault! Rosalie didn't do anything.
舅舅！這是我的錯！羅莎莉什麼也沒做過
Shut up! I've told you before, all traitors have to pay for their actions.
住口！我早已告訴妳，所有叛徒都要對他的行為負責
But you didn't have to do this to Rosalie!
但你也不必這樣對待羅莎莉！
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
住口！住口！住口！
I was too generous.
我太慷慨了
I never expected my niece to betray me like this.
我從未想過我的外甥女會這樣背叛我
You shall be punished!
妳將受到懲罰！
No... Stop.
不要...請停止
Please... Forgive me...
請你...饒了我吧...
Please...
求求你...
Give it to me.
把它給我
Huh?
啊？
Duke Dusee!
路積公爵！
Here.
在這兒
Everyone leave the room.
所有人給我離開這間房
Duke Dusee, what are you going to do?
路積公爵，你要做什麼？
Get out of here now!
立即離開這裡！
I'm going to make you keep your promise, Rachel.
我要妳遵守妳的承諾，莉露
NO!!
不要！
Just a little more, Rachel.
就再多少少，莉露
I know it's hard but hang on until the end.
我知道妳很辛苦，但仍要堅持到最後
You'll... Well...
妳會...沒事的...
Did it hurt?
痛嗎？
What?
啊？
Uncle?
舅舅？
How sad...
多麼令人哀傷...